5dfly.com 2018-05-14

# 5DFly Photo Design Software - Privacy policy

5DFly's Customer Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by 5DFly anytime you interact with 5DFly, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase 5DFly products and services, or when you contact our sales or support associates. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at 5DFly, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

## Why we collect personal information

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

## What information we collect and how we may use it 

There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better products or service. For example:

  * We may ask for your personal information when you're discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, downloading a software update, registering for a seminar, participating in an online survey, registering your products, or purchasing a product.
  * When you interact with 5DFly, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and information about the 5DFly products you own, such as their serial numbers and date of purchase; and information relating to a support or service issue. 
  * We also collect information for market research purposes — such as your occupation and where you use your computer - to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service. 
  * We collect information regarding customer activities on our websites. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites, products, and Internet services are of most interest to them. 
  * We may use personal information to provide products that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve 5DFly's products and service.

### Publicly displayed information is public

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on 5DFly website you should be aware that any information you share is visible to other users. Personally identifiable information you submit to one of these forums can be read, collected, or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages. 5DFly is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. For example, if you choose to make information, which was previously non-public, available by enabling certain user features, 5DFly will collect that information from your interaction and the information will become publicly available.

## When we disclose your information

5DFly takes your privacy very seriously. 5DFly does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers.

### Within the 5DFly Software Inc.

To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within the 5DFly Software globally who will take steps to safeguard it in accordance with 5DFly's privacy policy.

### With our service providers, vendors, and strategic partners

There are also times when it may be advantageous for 5DFly to make certain personal information about you available to companies that 5DFly has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for 5DFly to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with 5DFly's policies, except if we inform you otherwise at the time of collection. 

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

## How we protect your personal information

5DFly takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

5DFly uses secure server hosted by Paypal, SWREG and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information including name, address, credit card number credit card expiration date etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information.

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser like Safari.

## Kids

5DFly recognizes that parents, guardians, or other adults often purchase our products for family use, including use by minors. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 for marketing purposes, but because some information is collected electronically, it can appear to be the personal information of the 5DFly purchaser of the product, and will be treated as such by this privacy policy. If a child under 13 submits personal information to 5DFly and we learn that that personal information is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible.

## Cookies and other technologies

As is standard practice on many corporate websites, 5DFly's website uses "cookies" and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We also use cookies and other technologies to make sure that our online advertising is bringing customers to our products and services. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. And we use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 5DFly will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.

## Our companywide commitment to your privacy

This policy covers the 5DFly website and is applicable worldwide. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to 5DFly employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company. 

## International users

5DFly abides by the safe harbor framework set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information collected from the European Union. The following link provides more information about the [U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Program. ](http://www.export.gov/)

5DFly's website has links to the sites of other companies. 5DFly is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.
